<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<xml>
  <records>
    <record>
      <ref-type name="Conference Proceedings"></ref-type>
      <contributors>
        <authors>
          <author>
            Rai, Jitender
          </author>
          <author>
            Tripathi, R. C.
          </author>
          <author>
            Gulati, Nipun
          </author>
        </authors>
        <secondary-authors>
        </secondary-authors>
      </contributors>
      <titles>
        <title>A comparative study of implementing innovation in education sector due to COVID-19</title>
      </titles>
      <dates>
        <year>2020</year>
          <pub-dates>
            <date>12</date>
          </pub-dates>
      </dates>
      <pages>94-97</pages>
      <isbn>9781728189086</isbn>
      <electronic-resource-num>10.1109&#x2F;SMART50582.2020.9337148</electronic-resource-num>
      <abstract>This paper focuses on a Comparative Study of Implementing Innovation in Education Sector due to COVID-19. It focuses on the ability of Education Sector to change and adapt quickly, to be responsive to new technologies and methodologies and be flexible to the needs of the students, parents and government. Video meetings, online teaching, digital platforms, etc. are the technologies used to increase the growth of online education. So, I have defined the different analysis study based on earlier education system and new education system. A drastic change is predicted in the education sector.</abstract>
      <publisher>Institute of Electrical and Electronics Engineers Inc.</publisher>
      <periodical><full-title>Proceedings of the 2020 9th International Conference on System Modeling and Advancement in Research Trends, SMART 2020</full-title></periodical>
      <keywords>
        <keyword>Digital platforms</keyword>
        <keyword>Innovation</keyword>
        <keyword>Online teaching</keyword>
        <keyword>Technology, etc.</keyword>
        <keyword>Video meetings</keyword>
      </keywords>
      <urls>
        <related-urls>
        </related-urls>
      </urls>
    </record>
    <record>
      <ref-type name="Journal Article"></ref-type>
      <contributors>
        <authors>
          <author>
            Truong, Thanh Cong
          </author>
          <author>
            Diep, Quoc Bao
          </author>
        </authors>
        <secondary-authors>
        </secondary-authors>
      </contributors>
      <titles>
        <title>Technological Spotlights of Digital Transformation in Tertiary Education</title>
      </titles>
      <dates>
        <year>2023</year>
      </dates>
      <volume>11</volume>
      <pages>40954-40966</pages>
      <electronic-resource-num>10.1109&#x2F;ACCESS.2023.3270340</electronic-resource-num>
      <abstract>In the current globalization trend, digital transformation is an indispensable requirement that affects all aspects of life. Within the education domain, it creates opportunities for tertiary education institutions to replace traditional teaching, learning, research, and operation methods with more innovative, creative, and cost-effective methods. This article aims to examine recent technological advancements to promote the transformation in tertiary education. Our research methodology consists of two main activities: 1) identifying relevant literature on the use of technology to promote transformation in tertiary education by adopting PRISMA (Preferred Reporting Items for Systematic Reviews and Meta-Analyses) guidelines; 2) conducting a thematic analysis based on the findings of the literature review; to explore the relationships between them in order to better understand the link between technological trends and digital transformation in tertiary education. The findings indicate that the current technology trends that are being concerned and deployed in the educational environment are Artificial intelligence, the Internet of Things, blockchain technology, and other relevant platforms and technologies such as Social networks, Mobile platforms, Big data analytics, Cloud computing, Robotic Process Automation, Virtual reality and Augmented reality and Additive manufacturing. The article also discusses the adjustment of tertiary education in the process of digital transformation with the support of technology and points out the shortcomings as well as research directions in the coming time.</abstract>
      <publisher>Institute of Electrical and Electronics Engineers Inc.</publisher>
      <periodical><full-title>IEEE Access</full-title></periodical>
      <keywords>
        <keyword>Digital transformation</keyword>
        <keyword>technology</keyword>
        <keyword>tertiary education</keyword>
      </keywords>
      <urls>
        <related-urls>
        </related-urls>
      </urls>
    </record>
    <record>
      <ref-type name="Conference Proceedings"></ref-type>
      <contributors>
        <authors>
          <author>
            Naidu, Vikas Rao
          </author>
          <author>
            Bhatia, Satinder
          </author>
          <author>
            Hasan, Raza
          </author>
          <author>
            Singh, Baldev
          </author>
          <author>
            Jesrani, Karan
          </author>
          <author>
            Agarwal, Aparna
          </author>
        </authors>
        <secondary-authors>
        </secondary-authors>
      </contributors>
      <titles>
        <title>Smart Education Platform to Enhance Student Learning Experience during COVID-19</title>
      </titles>
      <dates>
        <year>2021</year>
      </dates>
      <isbn>9781665417037</isbn>
      <electronic-resource-num>10.1109&#x2F;ICRITO51393.2021.9596433</electronic-resource-num>
      <abstract>The community of learners of these days are highly motivated to use the latest trends in education due to the current demand of the education sector. When the Smart education scenario is observed, various advancements in Smart cities play a vital role. Situations like the current pandemic of COVID-19 has forced the entire community of learners to learn through online mode and most of the educational institutions are opting for this mode for a safe learning environment. Several tools are available to support this of which Zoom is one of the most popular online tools and many institutions are using Zoom for online activities related to teaching and learning practice. This paper shows the results of one of such practice implemented during the current situation including the infrastructure of Video Streaming Server utilizing recorded zoom meetings and Moodle. Data is collected by means of a survey conducted among the staff and students. Results have revealed that this practice has shown a good impact on flexibility, accessibility and innovation on learners. The engagement has a scope for improvement to motivate the learners.</abstract>
      <publisher>Institute of Electrical and Electronics Engineers Inc.</publisher>
      <periodical><full-title>2021 9th International Conference on Reliability, Infocom Technologies and Optimization (Trends and Future Directions), ICRITO 2021</full-title></periodical>
      <keywords>
        <keyword>online student interaction</keyword>
        <keyword>remote education</keyword>
        <keyword>smart cities</keyword>
        <keyword>video conference</keyword>
        <keyword>zoom</keyword>
      </keywords>
      <urls>
        <related-urls>
        </related-urls>
      </urls>
    </record>
    <record>
      <ref-type name="Conference Proceedings"></ref-type>
      <contributors>
        <authors>
          <author>
            Darvin, Arief
          </author>
          <author>
            Kosasih, Jeffry
          </author>
          <author>
            Stefanus
          </author>
          <author>
            Hanafiah, Novita
          </author>
        </authors>
        <secondary-authors>
        </secondary-authors>
      </contributors>
      <titles>
        <title>Usability Evaluation of Learning Management System</title>
      </titles>
      <dates>
        <year>2021</year>
      </dates>
      <pages>269-272</pages>
      <isbn>9781728133331</isbn>
      <electronic-resource-num>10.1109&#x2F;ICCSAI53272.2021.9609730</electronic-resource-num>
      <abstract>In the current era of globalization, there are a lot of things have been done with technology. One of them is education. LMS is an example implementation of technology in Education. LMS is a platform that provided by schools or universities, to support teaching and learning activities. Many literatures show that with the LMS, online learning can be fulfilled properly. To make an LMS comfortable and easy to use, it is necessary to have a good user interface design and user experience. User interface and user experience are a very important part of developing an LMS. Without a good user interface and user experience, the LMS cannot be used by the user properly. Based on the research, there are two methods commonly used to evaluate user interface design and user experience. Usability measurement and heuristic evaluation are two methods that are always used to evaluate user interface and user experience. In addition, there is an important part of the LMS, it was features. Based on the research, the most common features in LMS are discussion forums and learning materials. Therefore, users can discuss the materials each other and also share learning materials.</abstract>
      <publisher>Institute of Electrical and Electronics Engineers Inc.</publisher>
      <periodical><full-title>Proceedings of 2021 1st International Conference on Computer Science and Artificial Intelligence, ICCSAI 2021</full-title></periodical>
      <keywords>
        <keyword>Learning Management System</keyword>
        <keyword>User Experience</keyword>
        <keyword>User Interface</keyword>
      </keywords>
      <urls>
        <related-urls>
        </related-urls>
      </urls>
    </record>
    <record>
      <ref-type name="Conference Proceedings"></ref-type>
      <contributors>
        <authors>
          <author>
            Wang, Cheng Hung
          </author>
          <author>
            Wang, Ting Ya
          </author>
        </authors>
        <secondary-authors>
        </secondary-authors>
      </contributors>
      <titles>
        <title>E-learning platform of STEAM aesthetic course materials based on user experience</title>
      </titles>
      <dates>
        <year>2018</year>
          <pub-dates>
            <date>12</date>
          </pub-dates>
      </dates>
      <pages>123-128</pages>
      <isbn>9781538650592</isbn>
      <electronic-resource-num>10.1109&#x2F;IC3.2018.00-46</electronic-resource-num>
      <abstract>With the popularity of the Internet, lots of information is provided online, and the type of e-learning is becoming more multivariate. In order to enhance the use intention and learning performance, interface design not only has to the content, but also considers the user&#39;s behavior. Users&#39; prior knowledge or past experience will also affect their feeling and effectiveness as they are using. We integrated the concept of Kolb&#39;s experience learning circle into this e-learning platform, supplemented by modern interface design, and take usability and user experience as an evaluation consideration to plan and design this e-learning platform. Therefore, this study aims to explore the usability and user experience of users on this platform. In order to reduce the threshold of interdisciplinary learning and to improve learners&#39; use intention and learning performance. The results of this study can be reference for planning and design of STEAM learning website, or interdisciplinary learning materials.</abstract>
      <publisher>Institute of Electrical and Electronics Engineers Inc.</publisher>
      <periodical><full-title>Proceedings - 2018 1st International Cognitive Cities Conference, IC3 2018</full-title></periodical>
      <keywords>
        <keyword>Aesthetic experience</keyword>
        <keyword>E-learning</keyword>
        <keyword>Experiential learning</keyword>
        <keyword>STEAM education</keyword>
        <keyword>Usability</keyword>
        <keyword>User experience</keyword>
      </keywords>
      <urls>
        <related-urls>
        </related-urls>
      </urls>
    </record>
    <record>
      <ref-type name="Journal Article"></ref-type>
      <contributors>
        <authors>
          <author>
            Lei, Zhongcheng
          </author>
          <author>
            Zhou, Hong
          </author>
          <author>
            Hu, Wenshan
          </author>
          <author>
            Liu, Guo Ping
          </author>
        </authors>
        <secondary-authors>
        </secondary-authors>
      </contributors>
      <titles>
        <title>Unified and Flexible Online Experimental Framework for Control Engineering Education</title>
      </titles>
      <dates>
        <year>2022</year>
          <pub-dates>
            <date>1</date>
          </pub-dates>
      </dates>
      <volume>69</volume>
      <pages>835-844</pages>
      <issue>1</issue>
      <electronic-resource-num>10.1109&#x2F;TIE.2021.3053903</electronic-resource-num>
      <abstract>This article introduces a unified and flexible experimental framework for massive online experimentation of control education. The new architecture adopts a front-end and back-end separation scheme based on React at frontend and Nginx at backend, and a single page application has been achieved to improve user experience. Multiple features and supporting technologies which provide a flexible, interactive, and real-time platform with enhanced sense of presence and user experience are discussed. The design and implementation of the proposed system are depicted in detail. With the implementation of online algorithm design, the unified framework enables all the functionalities such as web-based algorithm design, parameter tuning, visual configuration of customized user interface, and real-time control with remote and virtual laboratories, which cover the entire process in control education experimentation. A case study with students from two universities shows that the implemented online laboratory framework can support massive students with minimum maintenance required.</abstract>
      <publisher>Institute of Electrical and Electronics Engineers Inc.</publisher>
      <periodical><full-title>IEEE Transactions on Industrial Electronics</full-title></periodical>
      <keywords>
        <keyword>Control engineering education</keyword>
        <keyword>flexibility and scalability</keyword>
        <keyword>online experimental framework</keyword>
        <keyword>online laboratory</keyword>
      </keywords>
      <urls>
        <related-urls>
        </related-urls>
      </urls>
    </record>
    <record>
      <ref-type name="Book"></ref-type>
      <contributors>
        <authors>
          <author>
            Ariwa, Ezendu
          </author>
          <author>
            IEEE Technology and Engineering Management Society.
          </author>
          <author>
            Institute of Electrical and Electronics Engineers
          </author>
        </authors>
        <secondary-authors>
        </secondary-authors>
      </contributors>
      <titles>
        <title>ICDIM 2018 : Thirteenth International Conference on Digital Information Management (ICDIM 2018) : Berlin, Germany, September 24-26, 2018.</title>
      </titles>
      <isbn>9781538652442</isbn>
      <abstract>&quot;IEEE Catalog Number: CFP18DIM-USB.&quot;</abstract>
      <keywords>
      </keywords>
      <urls>
        <related-urls>
        </related-urls>
      </urls>
    </record>
    <record>
      <ref-type name="Report"></ref-type>
      <contributors>
        <authors>
          <author>
            Riegel, Caitlin
          </author>
          <author>
            Kozen, Alice
          </author>
        </authors>
        <secondary-authors>
        </secondary-authors>
      </contributors>
      <titles>
        <title>ATTAINING 21ST CENTURY SKILLS IN A VIRTUAL CLASSROOM</title>
      </titles>
      <volume>41</volume>
      <issue>3</issue>
      <abstract>As society moves further into the 21st century and focuses on becoming more global, current and future learners will need to meet another set of requirements that are viewed as quality indicators and necessary dimensions for future success. These requirements are outlined by The National Education Association as the &quot;Four Cs&quot; of 21st century skills. They include communication, collaboration, critical thinking and problem solving, and creativity. Typically, these skills are taught in traditional settings as the instructor and students interact face-to-face. However, the &quot;Four Cs&quot; can be achieved in online environments as well through the use of various forms of technology. This article addresses teaching and learning the four quality indicators within a virtual classroom. Digital resources that address each of the &quot;Four Cs&quot; and tie into content learning are identified and described. Through the use of the recommended resources, virtual classrooms may have more to offer than seated classrooms in terms of attaining and becoming proficient in the 21st century skills. Further, these recommendations offer a valuable service for making online instruction more effective by way of a comprehensive list of digital resources.</abstract>
      <periodical><full-title>Educational Planning</full-title></periodical>
      <keywords>
      </keywords>
      <urls>
        <related-urls>
        </related-urls>
      </urls>
    </record>
    <record>
      <ref-type name="Conference Proceedings"></ref-type>
      <contributors>
        <authors>
          <author>
            Liu, Yue Tang
          </author>
          <author>
            Cheng, Pei Yu
          </author>
          <author>
            Shih, Sheng Pao
          </author>
          <author>
            Huang, Tai Yi
          </author>
        </authors>
        <secondary-authors>
        </secondary-authors>
      </contributors>
      <titles>
        <title>MetaClassroom: A WebXR-Based Hybrid Virtual Reality Classroom</title>
      </titles>
      <dates>
        <year>2023</year>
      </dates>
      <pages>280-281</pages>
      <isbn>9798350300543</isbn>
      <electronic-resource-num>10.1109&#x2F;ICALT58122.2023.00088</electronic-resource-num>
      <abstract>The primary objective of this study is to design and implement a virtual reality classroom that incorporates the OMO (Online Merge Offline) concept. Utilizing WebXR technology, a virtual reality classroom environment is created, enabling teachers and students to interact within this immersive space via various devices, including mobile phones, tablets, laptops, and VR devices. Currently, the system has established two virtual reality scenes in both classroom and discussion room settings to provide students and teachers with a highly realistic virtual reality classroom experience. It is worth mentioning that these virtual reality scenes have been tested by university students and instructors and received positive feedback.</abstract>
      <publisher>Institute of Electrical and Electronics Engineers Inc.</publisher>
      <periodical><full-title>Proceedings - 2023 IEEE International Conference on Advanced Learning Technologies, ICALT 2023</full-title></periodical>
      <keywords>
        <keyword>Virtual Classroom</keyword>
        <keyword>Virtual Reality</keyword>
        <keyword>WebXR</keyword>
      </keywords>
      <urls>
        <related-urls>
        </related-urls>
      </urls>
    </record>
    <record>
      <ref-type name="Conference Proceedings"></ref-type>
      <contributors>
        <authors>
          <author>
            Baibhav, Jayesh
          </author>
          <author>
            Ghatak, Jyotishman
          </author>
          <author>
            Mayan, J. Albert
          </author>
        </authors>
        <secondary-authors>
        </secondary-authors>
      </contributors>
      <titles>
        <title>Web based Payment Tracking and Accounting Application</title>
      </titles>
      <dates>
        <year>2023</year>
      </dates>
      <pages>1018-1022</pages>
      <isbn>9798350397253</isbn>
      <electronic-resource-num>10.1109&#x2F;ICICCS56967.2023.10142894</electronic-resource-num>
      <abstract>The Payment Tracking System (PTS) is a sophisticated web-based platform designed for proficiently tracking and managing payments from various vendors. It serves as a centralized hub for consolidating payment requests from the accounts department to upper management, thereby ensuring timely delivery of supplier payments through the implementation of integrated best practices for managing operations and services. The system boasts advanced Transaction Management functionality such as Invoice Generation and Payment Reminders, providing unparalleled visibility, insight, isolation, and swift resolution of payment-related issues for any type of organization by delivering the necessary information in a timely manner to the user. In today&#39;s fast-paced business environment, managing invoicing and chasing payments from clients can be a challenging task. This innovative application offers a solution to this problem by providing businesses with the capability to track payments from clients and gain valuable insights into their earnings. The system not only facilitates the creation, sending, and receiving of invoices, but also generates automated follow-up reminders for overdue payments. By utilizing this application, clients can also avoid incurring late fees</abstract>
      <publisher>Institute of Electrical and Electronics Engineers Inc.</publisher>
      <periodical><full-title>Proceedings of the 7th International Conference on Intelligent Computing and Control Systems, ICICCS 2023</full-title></periodical>
      <keywords>
        <keyword>Invoice</keyword>
        <keyword>Reminders</keyword>
        <keyword>Transaction Management</keyword>
      </keywords>
      <urls>
        <related-urls>
        </related-urls>
      </urls>
    </record>
    <record>
      <ref-type name="Conference Proceedings"></ref-type>
      <contributors>
        <authors>
          <author>
            Kostoski, Stefan
          </author>
          <author>
            Apostolova, Marika
          </author>
        </authors>
        <secondary-authors>
        </secondary-authors>
      </contributors>
      <titles>
        <title>Payatron - Secure electronic transaction processing system</title>
      </titles>
      <dates>
        <year>2021</year>
          <pub-dates>
            <date>6</date>
          </pub-dates>
      </dates>
      <isbn>9780738133614</isbn>
      <electronic-resource-num>10.1109&#x2F;MECO52532.2021.9459722</electronic-resource-num>
      <abstract>As online transactions continue to grow and become a significant part of the global economy, the ability to accept online payments is becoming more important for businesses. Each e-commerce provider should offer to the customers reliable and secure payment procedures. The procedures should ensure fast payments processing and minimizing the possibility for complains at same time. This would result in faster delivery of goods and encourage customer loyalty. In this paper we are going to present our custom developed system for processing electronic transactions (payment processor) - Payatron.</abstract>
      <publisher>Institute of Electrical and Electronics Engineers Inc.</publisher>
      <periodical><full-title>2021 10th Mediterranean Conference on Embedded Computing, MECO 2021</full-title></periodical>
      <keywords>
        <keyword>e-commerce</keyword>
        <keyword>payment</keyword>
        <keyword>payment gateway</keyword>
        <keyword>payment processor</keyword>
        <keyword>payment system</keyword>
        <keyword>secure</keyword>
        <keyword>transactions</keyword>
      </keywords>
      <urls>
        <related-urls>
        </related-urls>
      </urls>
    </record>
    <record>
      <ref-type name="Journal Article"></ref-type>
      <contributors>
        <authors>
          <author>
            Gochhwal, Rahul
          </author>
        </authors>
        <secondary-authors>
        </secondary-authors>
      </contributors>
      <titles>
        <title>Unified Payment Interface—An Advancement in Payment Systems</title>
      </titles>
      <dates>
        <year>2017</year>
      </dates>
      <volume>07</volume>
      <pages>1174-1191</pages>
      <issue>10</issue>
      <electronic-resource-num>10.4236&#x2F;ajibm.2017.710084</electronic-resource-num>
      <abstract>This paper studies Unified
Payment Interface (UPI), a new age payment system introduced in India by
National Payment Corporation of India. Unified Payment Interface is a mobile
centric, real time interbank payment system which has the potential to
transform and universalize digital payments in India. The paper traces the
evolution of payments systems in India and examines in detail the technology
behind Unified Payment Interface focusing on its architecture and security
systems through empirical and theoretical literature review. UPI is a
significant advancement as compared to extant payment system in terms of cost,
ease of use for consumers, settlement times and security and has witnessed good
user adoption. Its modular API based architecture will enable development of innovative
solutions for consumers and businesses. UPI is currently in its infancy stage
and development of merchant centric UPI solutions will greatly increase the
user adoption. UPI can help bring a large part of the population within the
ambit of digital economy and can be a great tool for financial inclusion in
India.</abstract>
      <publisher>Scientific Research Publishing, Inc,</publisher>
      <periodical><full-title>American Journal of Industrial and Business Management</full-title></periodical>
      <keywords>
      </keywords>
      <urls>
        <related-urls>
        </related-urls>
      </urls>
    </record>
    <record>
      <ref-type name="Conference Proceedings"></ref-type>
      <contributors>
        <authors>
          <author>
            Mohammed, Abubakar
          </author>
          <author>
            Kumar, Sanjeev
          </author>
          <author>
            Mu&#39;Azu, Hammandikko Gaya
          </author>
          <author>
            Kumar, Rajiv
          </author>
          <author>
            Shah, Praveen
          </author>
          <author>
            Memoria, Minakshi
          </author>
          <author>
            Rawat, Amarjeet
          </author>
          <author>
            Gupta, Ashulekha
          </author>
        </authors>
        <secondary-authors>
        </secondary-authors>
      </contributors>
      <titles>
        <title>Data Security and Protection: A Mechanism for Managing Data Theft and Cybercrime in Online Platforms of Educational Institutions</title>
      </titles>
      <dates>
        <year>2022</year>
      </dates>
      <pages>758-761</pages>
      <isbn>9781665496025</isbn>
      <electronic-resource-num>10.1109&#x2F;COM-IT-CON54601.2022.9850702</electronic-resource-num>
      <abstract>Advancement in technology has brought changes in educational institutions that leads to the adoption of several information system and online platforms. Students and staff were sharing important data through these platforms. This has exposed the institution to cybercrime activities by both internal and external agents of malicious users. Their motive is to gain access to the platforms in order to data related to fees and other academic records, or to distort the entire system to steal the data with the aim of committing an illicit transactions or activities. This paper aimed at providing security mechanism or model for data security and protection in educational institutions. It provides empirical studies related to data security and protection as well as cyberspace and online data theft in educational institutions. The paper recommends that educational institutions should adopt and implement the security mechanism and models to prevent cybercrime activities. It also recommends that sensitization should be organized for both students and staff on the use online platforms to prevent them from being exposed to malicious users.</abstract>
      <publisher>Institute of Electrical and Electronics Engineers Inc.</publisher>
      <periodical><full-title>2022 International Conference on Machine Learning, Big Data, Cloud and Parallel Computing, COM-IT-CON 2022</full-title></periodical>
      <keywords>
        <keyword>Cybercrime</keyword>
        <keyword>Cyberspace</keyword>
        <keyword>Data Security and Protection</keyword>
        <keyword>Educational Institution</keyword>
        <keyword>Online Platforms</keyword>
      </keywords>
      <urls>
        <related-urls>
        </related-urls>
      </urls>
    </record>
    <record>
      <ref-type name="Conference Proceedings"></ref-type>
      <contributors>
        <authors>
          <author>
            Chen, M. A.Jiayi
          </author>
          <author>
            Xu, Jingwei
          </author>
        </authors>
        <secondary-authors>
        </secondary-authors>
      </contributors>
      <titles>
        <title>Data Privacy Protection from the Perspective of GDPR - A Case Study on E-learning Platform &#39;SHCneo&#39;</title>
      </titles>
      <dates>
        <year>2022</year>
      </dates>
      <isbn>9781665488877</isbn>
      <electronic-resource-num>10.1109&#x2F;CISP-BMEI56279.2022.9980175</electronic-resource-num>
      <abstract>In order to avoid the risk of privacy leakage during using E-Learning platforms, E-Learning Platform &#39;SHCneo&#39; - jointly built by Chinese and German universities follows the most strict General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR) in EU for protecting the personal privacy of teachers and students. Based on the introduction of current network security development on E-Learning platforms in China and other countries, we use SHCneo as a case study, analyze the characteristics of GDPR&#39;s personal data privacy protection, try to explore the improvement of the data privacy security in online learning system, and summarize a few data privacy protection measures.</abstract>
      <publisher>Institute of Electrical and Electronics Engineers Inc.</publisher>
      <periodical><full-title>Proceedings - 2022 15th International Congress on Image and Signal Processing, BioMedical Engineering and Informatics, CISP-BMEI 2022</full-title></periodical>
      <keywords>
        <keyword>GDPR</keyword>
        <keyword>SHCneo</keyword>
        <keyword>data privacy protection</keyword>
      </keywords>
      <urls>
        <related-urls>
        </related-urls>
      </urls>
    </record>
    <record>
      <ref-type name="Conference Proceedings"></ref-type>
      <contributors>
        <authors>
          <author>
            Derawi, M
          </author>
        </authors>
        <secondary-authors>
        </secondary-authors>
      </contributors>
      <titles>
        <title>Securing e-learning platforms</title>
      </titles>
      <dates>
        <year>2014</year>
      </dates>
      <pages>1-4</pages>
      <electronic-resource-num>10.1109&#x2F;ICWOAL.2014.7009237</electronic-resource-num>
      <periodical><full-title>2014 International Conference on Web and Open Access to Learning (ICWOAL)</full-title></periodical>
      <keywords>
      </keywords>
      <urls>
        <related-urls>
        </related-urls>
      </urls>
    </record>
    <record>
      <ref-type name="Conference Proceedings"></ref-type>
      <contributors>
        <authors>
          <author>
            Birari, Abhijeet
          </author>
          <author>
            Yawalkar, Prajakta
          </author>
          <author>
            Janardanan, Rahul
          </author>
          <author>
            Subramani, Lakshmi
          </author>
          <author>
            Sharma, Rohit
          </author>
        </authors>
        <secondary-authors>
        </secondary-authors>
      </contributors>
      <titles>
        <title>Perception and Practices of EdTech Platform: A Sentiment Analysis</title>
      </titles>
      <dates>
        <year>2022</year>
      </dates>
      <isbn>9781665453615</isbn>
      <electronic-resource-num>10.1109&#x2F;TQCEBT54229.2022.10041491</electronic-resource-num>
      <abstract>Virtual and digital learning being the new normal, pandemic outburst and unexpected disruption in the functioning of educational services have paved way for online learning services. Considering the fast-Track growth of the education technology (EdTech) industry, in order to sustain, it is imperative for the industry to understand the underlying issues by capturing the end users&#39; perception. The primary purpose of this research is to examine the perception of users towards EdTech platforms A sample of 600 reviews regarding three major EdTech platforms were scraped from MouthShut.com as textual data and analysed using lexicon-based method. The polarity of the sentiments pertaining to the reviews of different platforms was analysed using sentiment analysis. Furthermore, the topic modelling on the reviews was performed using natural language programming. The results revealed a positive sentiment of users towards the EdTech services and platforms. The most influential factors are faculty expertise, interface user-friendliness, syllabus, and pricing model. Our findings help EdTech service providers to understand which factors are driving this dramatic shift in student behaviour so they may develop better strategies to attract and retain consumers. Despite the rise in EdTech platform popularity, this is the first study to investigate perception of EdTech users comprehensively.</abstract>
      <publisher>Institute of Electrical and Electronics Engineers Inc.</publisher>
      <periodical><full-title>2022 International Conference on Trends in Quantum Computing and Emerging Business Technologies, TQCEBT 2022</full-title></periodical>
      <keywords>
        <keyword>EdTech platfornb Perception</keyword>
        <keyword>Online Learning Services</keyword>
        <keyword>Sentiment Analysis</keyword>
      </keywords>
      <urls>
        <related-urls>
        </related-urls>
      </urls>
    </record>
    <record>
      <ref-type name="Conference Proceedings"></ref-type>
      <contributors>
        <authors>
          <author>
            Paul, Rinika
          </author>
          <author>
            Rashmi, M. R.
          </author>
        </authors>
        <secondary-authors>
        </secondary-authors>
      </contributors>
      <titles>
        <title>Student Satisfaction and Churn Predicting using Machine Learning Algorithms for EdTech course</title>
      </titles>
      <dates>
        <year>2022</year>
      </dates>
      <isbn>9781665474337</isbn>
      <electronic-resource-num>10.1109&#x2F;ICRITO56286.2022.9965116</electronic-resource-num>
      <abstract>EdTech courses are believed to provide industry-oriented practical skills to the students to bridge the gap between academics and the industry. They also provide supporting education to the students to crack competitive exams in various sectors. With education institutions being shut down due to lockdown and moved to online mode, many students enrolled themselves in EdTech courses online creating competition amongst EdTech organizations. Reduced prices at times lead to reduced quality of the course content and the delivery. Students are often the prey in the competition who are left unsatisfied with the course and would never return to the organization for further courses leading to a churn. At least 50% of college students enroll in online courses in India but the completion rate is only about 13% which is very low. Customer churn is a major challenge to an organization reducing their growth as well as revenue. Two different machine learning algorithms viz. K-Nearest Neighbor (KNN) and Support Vector Machines (SVM) are proposed in this paper to predict the churn rate of students for EdTech courses based on the feedback of the students collected through the course end survey. The model also tells if the student is interested to enroll further in any other courses offered by the organization or refer the courses to their friends or relatives. The data is collected in real-time based on the online courses offered by a startup company and the churn rate for the organization is calculated.</abstract>
      <publisher>Institute of Electrical and Electronics Engineers Inc.</publisher>
      <periodical><full-title>2022 10th International Conference on Reliability, Infocom Technologies and Optimization (Trends and Future Directions), ICRITO 2022</full-title></periodical>
      <keywords>
        <keyword>Churn Prediction</keyword>
        <keyword>E-Learning</keyword>
        <keyword>EdTech Course</keyword>
        <keyword>K-Nearest Neighbor (KNN)</keyword>
        <keyword>Machine Learning (ML)</keyword>
        <keyword>Student Attrition</keyword>
        <keyword>Student Satisfaction</keyword>
        <keyword>Support Vector Machine (SVM)</keyword>
      </keywords>
      <urls>
        <related-urls>
        </related-urls>
      </urls>
    </record>
    <record>
      <ref-type name="Journal Article"></ref-type>
      <contributors>
        <authors>
          <author>
            Bilal, Muhammad
          </author>
          <author>
            Marjani, Mohsen
          </author>
          <author>
            Lali, Muhammad Ikramullah
          </author>
          <author>
            Malik, Nadia
          </author>
          <author>
            Gani, Abdullah
          </author>
          <author>
            Hashem, Ibrahim Abaker Targio
          </author>
        </authors>
        <secondary-authors>
        </secondary-authors>
      </contributors>
      <titles>
        <title>Profiling users&#39; behavior, and identifying important features of review &#39;helpfulness&#39;</title>
      </titles>
      <dates>
        <year>2020</year>
      </dates>
      <volume>8</volume>
      <pages>77227-77244</pages>
      <electronic-resource-num>10.1109&#x2F;ACCESS.2020.2989463</electronic-resource-num>
      <abstract>The increasing volume of online reviews and the use of review platforms leave tracks that can be used to explore interesting patterns. It is in the primary interest of businesses to retain and improve their reputation. Reviewers, on the other hand, tend to write reviews that can influence and attract people&#39;s attention, which often leads to deliberate deviations from past rating behavior. Until now, very limited studies have attempted to explore the impact of user rating behavior on review helpfulness. However, there are more perspectives of user behavior in selecting and rating businesses that still need to be investigated. Moreover, previous studies gave more attention to the review features and reported inconsistent findings on the importance of the features. To fill this gap, we introduce new and modify existing business and reviewer features and propose a user-focused mechanism for review selection. This study aims to investigate and report changes in business reputation, user choice, and rating behavior through descriptive and comparative analysis. Furthermore, the relevance of various features for review helpfulness is identified by correlation, linear regression, and negative binomial regression. The analysis performed on the Yelp dataset shows that the reputation of the businesses has changed slightly over time. Moreover, 46% of the users chose a business with a minimum of 4 stars. The majority of users give 4-star ratings, and 60% of reviewers adopt irregular rating behavior. Our results show a slight improvement by using user rating behavior and choice features. Whereas, the significant increase in R2 indicates the importance of reviewer popularity and experience features. The overall results show that the most significant features of review helpfulness are average user helpfulness, number of user reviews, average business helpfulness, and review length. The outcomes of this study provide important theoretical and practical implications for researchers, businesses, and reviewers.</abstract>
      <publisher>Institute of Electrical and Electronics Engineers Inc.</publisher>
      <periodical><full-title>IEEE Access</full-title></periodical>
      <keywords>
        <keyword>Business reputation</keyword>
        <keyword>crowd-sourced reviews</keyword>
        <keyword>rating behavior</keyword>
        <keyword>review helpfulness</keyword>
        <keyword>user profiling</keyword>
      </keywords>
      <urls>
        <related-urls>
        </related-urls>
      </urls>
    </record>
  </records>
</xml>